A Finding Aid to the Cranmer Art Group Records, circa 1980-2021, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Client Files, 1980-2021; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 55.2 Linear feet Boxes 1-54, 75
  - Client Files, 2003, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 8-9)
  - Client Files, 2003, Roy Lichtenstein Estate, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2003, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 11-12)
  - Client Files, 2003, Barbara Mathes Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2003, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 14-15)
  - Client Files, 2003, Jose Mugrabi (Brice Marden), Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2003, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 17-18)
  - Client Files, 2003, The Noguchi Museum (Isamu Noguchi), Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2003, O'Toole and Ewald (Willem de Kooning, "Greece on Eighth Avenue"), 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2003, P, 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 21-22)
  - Client Files, 2003, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2003, Robert Rauschenberg Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 24-25)
  - Client Files, 2003, Michael Rosenfeld Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2003, Judith Rothschild Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2003, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 2-5)
  - Client Files, 2003, Richard Serra, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2003, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
  - Client Files, 2003, U-Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 9-10)
  - Client Files, 2003, Jonathan Zuhovitsky, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 11-13)
  - Client Files, 2004, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 14-15)
  - Client Files, 2004, Axa Gallery and Le Bernardin, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 16-17)
  - Client Files, 2004, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 18-19)
  - Client Files, 2004, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 20-21)
  - Client Files, 2004, Paula Cooper Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2004, The Cramer Company, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 23-24)
  - Client Files, 2004, D-E, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2004, Dedalus Foundation, Inc. (Robert Motherwell), Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2004, Willem de Kooning Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2004, Eastman and Eastman, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2004, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 2004, Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2004, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
  - Client Files, 2004, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 7-8)
  - Client Files, 2004, Jim Hodges Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2004, I-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2004, Knoedler and Company, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2004, Ellsworth Kelly, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2004, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2004, Roy Lichtenstein Estate, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2004, Locksley Shea, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2004, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 16-18)
  - Client Files, 2004, Donald Marron (Franz Kline), Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2004, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 20-22)
  - Client Files, 2004, David Mirvish, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2004, Modernism Fine Arts, Inc. and Walter Maibaum, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2004, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2004, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - Client Files, 2004, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
  - Client Files, 2004, Robert Rauschenberg Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2004, Rockefeller University (Kenneth Noland), 1991, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2004, Andrea Rosen Gallery, 1991, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2004, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 8-10)
  - Client Files, 2004, Jay Shidler, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 11-13)
  - Client Files, 2004, T-U, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2004, V, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2004, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2004, Jonathan Zuhovitzky, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 17-22)
  - Client Files, 2005, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 23-24)
  - Client Files, 2005, Michael Black, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - Client Files, 2005, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
  - Client Files, 2005, Betty Cunningham Gallery (Agnes Martin), Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2005, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2005, Dedalus Foundation, Inc. (Robert Motherwell), Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2005, Willem de Kooning Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2005, E, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2005, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2005, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 11-12)
  - Client Files, 2005, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 13-14)
  - Client Files, 2005, Mary Heilmann, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD). (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2005, Perk Hixson, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2005, J, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2005, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 18-19)
  - Client Files, 2005, Roy Lichtenstein Estate and Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 20-21)
  - Client Files, 2005, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 22-23)
  - Client Files, 2005, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 24-26)
  - Client Files, 2005, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 27-28)
  - Client Files, 2005, Dennis Miller (Robert Kushner), Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2005, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2005, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 3-5)
  - Client Files, 2005, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
  - Client Files, 2005, Robert Rauschenberg Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2005, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 9-11)
  - Client Files, 2005, The Shidler Group, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 12-15)
  - Client Files, 2005, Thomas Sills Estate, Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD). (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2005, T-U, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2005, V-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2005, Jonathan Zuhovitzky, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 19-20)
  - 2006, Lists of Works Approved for Treatment, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2006, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2006, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 23-25)
  - Client Files, 2006, Peder Bonnier, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2006, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 27-28)
  - Client Files, 2006, Christie's, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2006, Paula Cooper Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2006, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
  - Client Files, 2006, Dedalus Foundation, Inc. (Robert Motherwell), Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 5-7)
  - Client Files, 2006, Willem de Kooning Foundation and Johanna Liesbeth de Kooning Trust, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 8-9)
  - Client Files, 2006, E, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2006, Estate of Lee V. Eastman and Christie's, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2006, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2006, Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2006, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 14-16)
  - Client Files, 2006, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 17-19)
  - Client Files, 2006, I-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 20-21)
  - Client Files, 2006, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 22-23)
  - Client Files, 2006, Knoedler and Company, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 24-25)
  - Client Files, 2006, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2006, Roy Lichtenstein Estate and Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2006, Locksley Shea, Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 2006, Locksley Shea (Brice Marden), 2000, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 2006, M, 2000, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Client Files, 2006, M, 2000, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2006, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 2-3)
  - Client Files, 2006, N, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2006, O, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2006, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 6-7)
  - Client Files, 2006, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 8-9)
  - Client Files, 2006, Robert Rauschenberg Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2006, Judith Rothschild Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 11-12)
  - Client Files, 2006, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 13-15)
  - Client Files, 2006, The Shidler Group, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 16-17)
  - Client Files, 2006, Richard Serra, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2006, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2006, V, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2006, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2006, Jonathan Zuhovitzky, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 22-23)
  - Client Files, 2007, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2007, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2007, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 26-27)
  - Client Files, 2007, D-E, Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 2007, Dedalus Foundation, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 1-8)
  - Client Files, 2007, Eastman, Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2007, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 10-11)
  - Client Files, 2007, Helen Frankenthaler, Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2007, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 13-14)
  - Client Files, 2007, H, Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD). (Box 30, Folder 15-16)
  - Client Files, 2007, Mary Heilmann, Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2007, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 18-19)
  - Client Files, 2007, Jedermann, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2007, Knoedler and Company, Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2007, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 22-23)
  - Client Files, 2007, Locks Foundation (Robert Motherwell), Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2007, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 25-27)
  - Client Files, 2007, Minagawa Art Lines, Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 2007, Modernism Fine Arts, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
  - Client Files, 2007, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 3-4)
  - Client Files, 2007, N-Q, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
  - Client Files, 2007, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2007, Robert Rauschenberg Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2007, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 9-11)
  - Client Files, 2007, Richard Serra and Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2007, The Shidler Group, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 13-14)
  - Client Files, 2007, Sotheby's, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2007, Sperone Westwater, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2007, Kristy Stubbs Gallery (Damien Hirst), Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2007, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 18-19)
  - Client Files, 2007, V, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2007, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 21-22)
  - 2008, Expenses and Lists of Clients, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2008, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2008, Aero, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2008, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 26-27)
  - Client Files, 2008, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 2008, Dedalus Foundation, Inc. (Robert Motherwell), Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 2008, Willem de Kooning Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2008, Dorsky Galleries, Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CDs). (Box 32, Folder 2-4)
  - Client Files, 2008, E, Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2008, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
  - Client Files, 2008, Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2008, Helen Frankenthaler, Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CDs). (Box 32, Folder 9-11)
  - Client Files, 2008, G, Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD). (Box 32, Folder 12-13)
  - Client Files, 2008, Guggenheim Bilbao Museum Foundation (Cy Twombly), Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2008, H-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2008, Mary Heilmann, Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2008, Judd Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2008, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2008, Debbie Kaufman, Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD). (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2008, Knoedler and Company, Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2008, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 21-24)
  - Client Files, 2008, Jean Charles Lignel (Andy Warhol), Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2008, Locksley Shea, Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD). (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2008, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 27-28)
  - Client Files, 2008, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD). (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
  - Client Files, 2008, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 2008, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2008, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2008, Robert Rauschenberg Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2008, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 7-8)
  - Client Files, 2008, The Shidler Group, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 9-11)
  - Client Files, 2008, Tony Smith Estate, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2008, T-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2008, David Teiger, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2008, TishmanSpeyer Properties, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2008, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2008, Y-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2009, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2009, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 19-20)
  - Client Files, 2009, C-D, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2009, Christie's, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2009, Willem de Kooning Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 23-24)
  - Client Files, 2009, E-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2009, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2009, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2009, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2009, Mary Heilmann, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 2009, Marlene Hess and Jim Zirin, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 4-9)
  - Client Files, 2009, I-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2009, The Jewish Museum (Robert Motherwell), Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2009, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2009, Knoedler and Company, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2009, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2009, Lennon Weinberg, Inc. (Joan Mitchell), Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2009, Roy Lichtenstein (Robert Rauschenberg), Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2009, Judy Liff, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 17-18)
  - Client Files, 2009, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 19-20)
  - Client Files, 2009, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2009, N, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2009, O, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2009, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2009, Plane Image, Inc. (Brice Marden), Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2009, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2009, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2009, Robert Rauschenberg Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2009, Richard Serra Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 2009, The Shidler Group, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2009, David Teiger, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2009, TishmanSpeyer Properties, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2009, T-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2009, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2010, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2010, Jennifer Blaikie, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2010, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 11-12)
  - Client Files, 2010, Cowles Charitable Trust, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2010, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2010, Dedalus Foundation, Inc. (Robert Motherwell), Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2010, Johanna Liesbeth de Kooning Trust (Willem de Kooning), Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2010, E-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2010, Eastman and Eastman, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2010, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2010, Galerie Lelong (Nancy Spero), Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2010, H-I, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2010, Hauser and Wirth, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2010, Mary Heilmann, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2010, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2010, JBBO, LLC (Jo Baer), Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2010, Jedermann, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2010, Knoedler and Company, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 27-28)
  - Client Files, 2010, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 2010, Lennon Weinberg, Inc. (Joan Mitchell), Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Client Files, 2010, Roy Lichtenstein Estate, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Client Files, 2010, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Client Files, 2010, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Client Files, 2010, Meringoff Equities, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2010, Thordis Moeller, Inc. (Blinky Palermo), Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2010, N, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 2010, Jay Newman, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2010, David Novros, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2010, O, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2010, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2010, Philadelphia Museum of Art (Ellsworth Kelly, "Lake II"), Archival Resource Key; Includes 2 electronic discs (CDs). (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2010, Plane Image, Inc. (Brice Marden), Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2010, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2010, Robert Rauschenberg Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2010, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2010, Richard Serra Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 13-14)
  - Client Files, 2010, The Shidler Group, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2010, Stella Maris (Julian Schnabel), Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD). (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2010, T-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2010, TishmanSpeyer Properties, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2010, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2010, David Zwirner Gallery (Brice Marden), Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD). (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2011, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2011, Bank of America (Ellsworth Kelly), Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2011, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 23-24)
  - Client Files, 2011, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2011, Dia Art Foundation (Blinky Palermo), Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2011, Johanna Liesbeth de Kooning Trust (Willem de Kooning), Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2011, E-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 2011, Kathy Fuld (Ellsworth Kelly), Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 2011, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 30-31)
  - Client Files, 2011, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Client Files, 2011, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
  - Client Files, 2011, James Hodges, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 2011, I, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2011, J, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 5)